Finding Aid for Howard Cyrus Lawrence Papers 1916-1966
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Howard Cyrus Lawrence Papers
1916-1966
Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.
Grand Rapids, Michigan businessman and Republican politician. Correspondence, business records, speeches, and other papers relating to state politics, charitable and civic interests, banking issues, the Grand Rapids Varnish Corporation, the Michigan Trust Company of Grand Rapids, and the Ypsilanti-Reed Furniture Company of Ionia, Michigan; also materials on Albion College, the Methodist Church, the Ionia Free Fair, and Republican Party politics, especially the campaign of Arthur H, Vandenberg for the presidency in 1940.
851795 Aa 2; AC
25 linear feet
2 oversize volumes
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Mrs. Clara L. Lawrence (donor no. 4241 ) and came to the library 1966-1967. One scrapbook, received in 1984, was given to the library by C. David Tompkins.
The collection is open for research.
Howard C. Lawrence, born August 14, 1890, was a Grand Rapids-based manufacturer and banker. Lawrence graduated from Lake Odessa High School in 1910, then in June 1911 entered the employ of the Lake Odessa State Savings Bank where he remained for ten years working his way up from bookkeeper and assistant cashier to president. In 1921, he became associated with Fred W. Green in the Ypsilanti Reed Furniture Company of Ionia, Michigan. He was first made assistant secretary-treasurer and later secretary-treasurer of the furniture company.
Lawrence service to state government began as executive secretary to Governor Fred Green, 1927-1930. In 1930, he was elected state treasurer, serving one term 1931-1932. He was later named to work with the state banking department as receiver of different banks and then as state banking commissioner, 1936-1937.
Beginning in the 1920s, Lawrence had served with the Ionia County Republican Committee. In 1929, he was elected chairman of the Michigan Republican State Central Committee serving until 1937. In 1940, he was manager of Arthur Vandenberg's campaign for president at the Republican National Convention.
Lawrence now returned to the private sector as vice president and director of the Michigan Trust Company of Grand Rapids, 1937-1944; as director, president and General Manager of the Grand Rapids Varnish Corporation; and as vice president and director of the Lake Odessa Canning Company.
Lawrence's civic positions included membership on the board of trustees of Albion College and director of the Grand Rapids Y.M.C.A. He died May 20, 1961.
The collection documents the business, civic, and political interests of Howard C. Lawrence. The series in the collection are: Correspondence; Speeches and speech material; Financial; Business Interests; Charitable and Civic Interests; Clippings; Miscellaneous; Photographs; and Notebooks.
Subjects:
Albion College.; American Bankers Association.; Banks and banking--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Business records.; Clergy--Michigan.; Depressions--1929--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Fairs--Michigan--Ionia County.; First Methodist Church (Grand Rapids, Mich.); Furniture industry and trade--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Grand Rapids (Mich.); Grand Rapids Varnish Corporation.; Ionia (Mich.); Ionia County Free Fair (Mich.); Lake Odessa (Mich.); Lake Odessa Canning Company.; Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.; Methodist Church (U.S.); Methodist Church (U.S.)--Michigan--Grand Rapids.MichiganGrand Rapids.; Methodist Church (U.S.). Michigan Conference.; Michigan. Banking Division.; Michigan. Dept. of Treasury.; Michigan Bankers Association.; Michigan--Politics and government--1929-1938.; Michigan--Politics and government--1939-1945.; Michigan--Politics and government--1946-1960.; Michigan--Politics and government--1837-1950.; Michigan--Politics and government--1951-; Michigan Trust Company (Grand Rapids, Mich.); Paint industry and trade--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Republican Party (Mich.); Ypsilanti-Reed Furniture Company (Ionia, Mich.); World War, 1939-1945.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Buildings--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.; Grand Rapids (Mich.)--Buildings.; Grand Rapids (Mich.)--Industrial buildings.; Grand Rapids Varnish Corporation.; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Industrial buildings--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Interiors.; Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-1987.; Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.; Michigan. State Administrative Board.; Offices.; Politics and government--Michigan--1939-1945.; Republican National Convention (22nd: 1940: Philadelphia, Pa.); Republican Party (Mich.). State Central Committee.; Varnishing industry.
Contributors:
Adams, Evyn.; Anderson, Charles F.; Andrews, Harold F.; Andrews, Roger, 1874-; Atwood, Orville E., 1880-; Baldwin, R. W.; Barnes, M. H.; Bass, Louis.; Battley, Joseph F., 1893-; Bicknell, John W.; Blodgett, John Wood, 1860-1951.; Blood, W. J.; Brake, D. Hale, 1891-1979; Bricker, John W. (John William), 1893-1986.; Bridges, Styles, 1898-1961.; Brown, Harry J.; Brown, Prentiss M. (Prentiss Marsh), 1889-1973.; Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.; Brundage, Ray O., 1881-; Bryant, Everett.; Butler, Leslie A.; Chapman, Fred A., 1878-1938.; Closterhouse, Leon T.; Cochran, Friend Morris, 1897-; Cochrane, Donald F., 1881-; Coors, D. Stanley, 1889-; Crawford, Fred L., 1888-1957.; Cudlip, William B., 1904-1988; Davies, B. L.; Dean, Walter Clark, 1898-; Degan, James E.; Deyo, Harry N., 1892-; Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.; Dodge, Joseph M. (Joseph Morrell), 1890-1964.; Dunckel, Miller Lewis, 1899-; Emery, John Garfield, 1881-; Fead, Louis H., 1877-1943.; Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.; Field, Howard A.; Fink, George Rupert, 1886-; Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.; Fleenor, Wayne Harrison, 1902-; Flynn, Felix H. H., 1881-; Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006.; Frey, James G.; Fritsche, Carl B.; Frost, Joseph D., 1888-; Gill, Etta Margaret Lawrence, 1919-; Glass, Harry.; Goebel, Paul Gordon, 1901-; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Green, Helen A. Kelly.; Groesbeck, Alexander J. (Alexander Joseph), 1873-1953.; Hager, Joseph A.; Hamilton, John Daniel Miller, 1892-; Hayes, H. Jaye.; Hekman, Edward John, 1914-; Hewitt, Charles Henry, 1900-; Hill, Merrick.; Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.; Hollinshead, Kenneth J.; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; Huckle, Thomas O., 1881-; Innis, Ralph B.; Jayne, Ira Waite, 1882-; Jonkman, Bartel J. (Bartel John), 1884-1955.; Kelly, Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-1971.; Kilpatrick, Lester A.; Kimball, LeRoy Elwood, 1888-; Kingston, George B.; Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.; Kresge, Sebastian Spering, 1867-1966.; Kresge, Stanley Sebastian, 1900-; Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-1987.; Lang, Samuel.; Lawrence, Gordon D., 1930-; Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1916-; Lawrence, Luther E., 1914-; Lawrence, Paul R.; Lawrence, Walter A., 1932-; Leffler, Emil, 1899-; Lillie, Guy.; Linderholm, C. Lincoln.; Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1902-1985; Lonergan, Augustine, 1874-1947.; McCartner, W. C.; McCrea, Archie Elbert, 1880-; McCurdy, Allan.; McKay, Frank D., 1883-; Mapes, Carl Edgar, 1874-1939.; Marin, Fredrik, 1898-; Mayberry, William A.; Moody, Blair, 1902-1954.; Moore, Andrew L., 1870-; Morgenthau, Henry, 1856-1946.; Moulton, Vern, 1880-; Newhall, R. Frank, 1874-; Nicholson, Walter G.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Norris, Louis William, 1906-; North, Walter Harper, 1871-1952.; Nowicki, Leo J., 1904-; Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860.; Ott, Harvey N.; Owen, R. Dwight.; Pahl, Marvin F.; Pollock, James K. (James Kerr), 1898-1968; Potter, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1916-1979.; Potter, William W., 1869-1940.; Pryor, Millard H., 1901-; Putnam, Mark Edson, 1886-; Reagan, Ronald.; Reed, Marshall Russell, 1891-; Reichert, Rudolph Edward, 1887-1965.; Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.; Seaton, John Lawrence, 1873-; Sebastian, James R.; Shackleton, James M., 1896-; Sharp, Alexander Jefferson.; Sharpe, Nelson, 1858-1935.; Sigler, Kim, b. 1894.; Sink, Charles A. (Charles Albert), 1879-1972.; Sligh, Charles R., Jr. (Charles Robert), 1906-1997; Slocum, William W., 1891-; Smith, Delos Grosvenor, 1893-; Stassen, Harold E. (Harold Edward), 1907-2001; Stough, Irvin K.; Stowe, Ernest A., b. 1859.; Summerfield, Arthur Ellsworth, 1899-1972.; Taylor, Malcolm Cameron, 1900-; Thompson, George.; Thompson, Harold R.; Thomson, James Francis, 1892-; Toncray, Richard.; Toy, Harry Stanley, 1892-1955.; Trautman, Paul R.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Vandenberg, Arthur Hendrick, 1907-1968.; Vander Werp, Don, 1885-; VanOstenburg, Neal.; Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-; Voorhies, Paul Warren, 1875-1952.; Wade, Raymond J., Bishop, 1875-; Waldo, Dwight Bryant, 1864-1939.; Walker, Louis Carlisle, 1875-1963.; Watts, Frank B.; Weber, Al H., 1870-; Westerman, Leland.; Whitehouse, William Whitcomb, 1891-; Wier, E. G.; Williams, Allan M. (Allan Mackenzie), 1892-1979.; Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-1988.; Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944.; Woodruff, Roy Orchard, 1876-1953.; Wright, James F.; Ziegler, Charles M., 1888-1959.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.
- Correspondence
  - 1917-February 1936, 29 folders (Box 1)
  - March 1936-December 1936, 28 folders (Box 2)
  - January-February 1937 (Box 3)
    (regarding his election as vice president of the Michigan Trust Company, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
  - January 1937-December 1939, 34 folders (Box 3)
  - January 1940-September 1940, 26 folders (Box 4)
  - October 1940-June 15, 1941, 17 folders (Box 5)
  - June 16, 1941-May 1942, 27 folders (Box 6)
  - June 1942-December 1943, 28 folders (Box 7)
  - January 1944-June 1945, 35 folders (Box 8)
  - July 1945-April 1947, 31 folders (Box 9)
  - May 1947-July 1948, 30 folders (Box 10)
  - August 1948-October 1949, 25 folders (Box 11)
  - November 1949-December 1951, 30 folders (Box 12)
  - January 1952-June 1953, 33 folders (Box 13)
  - July 1953-August 1954, 30 folders (Box 14)
  - September 1954-November 1955, 28 folders (Box 15)
  - January 1956-August 1957, 28 folders (Box 16)
  - October 1957-December 1959, 32 folders (Box 17)
  - Undated, 1960-1966; 34 folders (Box 18)
- Speeches and speech materials
  - 1931-1956, undated; 10 folders (Box 19)
- Financial
  - Expense accounts, 1940-1945 (Box 19)
  - Bills, receipts, etc.
    - 1934-1940 (Box 19)
    - 1951-1955 (Box 19)
    - 1956-1960 (Box 19)
    - 1961 (Box 19)
- Business Interests
  - Binghamton Ice and Storage Company, New York financial materials, 1935; 1937; undated (Box 19)
  - Lake Odessa Canning Company, Lake Odessa, Michigan financial papers, 1939; 1941; 1945 (Box 19)
  - Grand Rapids Varnish Company
    - 1938-1940 (Box 19)
    - 1939-1952 (Box 19)
    - 1941-1945 (Box 19)
    - 1946-1950 (Box 19)
    - 1951 (Box 19)
    - 1952 (Box 19)
    - 1953 (Box 19)
    - 1954 (Box 19)
    - 1955 (Box 19)
    - 1955-1960 (Box 19)
    - 1961 (Box 19)
    - Undated, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Banking
    - 1935-1955 (Box 20)
    - Trust funds, 1936 (Box 20)
    - Michigan Trust Company, 1939-1946 (Box 20)
    - Michigan Bankers Association, 1940-1950; undated (Box 20)
- Charitable and Civic Interests
  - Mailing lists, 1941 (Box 20)
  - Grand Rapids (miscellaneous), 1939-1961 (Box 20)
  - Community Chest in Grand Rapids, 1939-1942 (Box 20)
  - Civilian Air Force Committee, 1942 (Box 20)
  - Fund raising during World War II, 1942-1945 (Box 20)
  - Committees and clubs, circa 1942-1948; 1956 (Box 20)
  - Butterworth Hospital in Grand Rapids, 1944-1949 (Box 20)
  - City planning in Grand Rapids, 1948 (Box 20)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 20)
    - 1941 (Box 20)
    - 1942 (Box 20)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 20)
    - 1950s-1960 (Box 20)
    - Undated (Box 20)
  - Methodist Church
    - General, circa 1936-1957 (Box 20)
    - Membership lists, 1942-1961 (Box 20)
    - Methodist Ministers Pension Fund, 1945-1949; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Scrapbook re Methodist Ministers Pension Fund, 1946 (Volume 1)
    - Financial materials, 1957-1961 (Box 20)
  - Political campaigns, etc.
    - 1930s, 1940s (Box 21)
    - 1930s, 1940s (political campaigns) (Box 21)
    - (Republican Party), 1935-1940s (Box 21)
    - (state and national government), 1935-1947 (Box 21)
    - (Senator A. H. Vandenberg), 1939-1940s (Box 21)
    - Scrapbook regarding Republican National Convention and the Vandenberg candidacy (Volume 2)
      (mainly clippings with a few pamphlets and photographs of Lawrence on the convention floor)
  - Ionia Free Fair
    - General, 1935-1955 (Box 21)
    - Pamphlets, 1939-1941; 1945 (Box 21)
  - Speech by Ronald Reagan, and sermon concerning a Catholic becoming President of the United States, 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Michigan College Foundation, 1945-1949 (Box 21)
  - Albion College
    - 1939-1960, undated (Box 21)
    - (Financial committee), 1941-1960; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - (Board of Trustees), 1935-1961 (Box 21)
    - (finances), 1935-1955; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - 1938-1959, undated; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - (Goodrich Chapel), 1957-1958 (Box 21)
    - (business manager), 1935-1954 (Box 22)
    - (reports of the president), 1936-1945 (Box 22)
    - 1936, 1947, undated (reports of special committees of Albion College) (Box 22)
    - (reports of the president), 1946-1957 (Box 22)
    - (reports), 1947-1961; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Pamphlets, 1940s; 1950s (Box 22)
      (include financial information, issues of Triumphe, Albion's alumni magazine, and other promotional literature)
- Clippings
  - 1928 (Box 23)
  - 1932-1935 (Box 23)
  - 1936 (Box 23)
  - 1937 (Box 23)
  - 1938 (Box 23)
  - 1939 (Box 23)
  - 1940 (Box 23)
  - 1941 (Box 23)
  - 1942 (Box 23)
  - 1943 (Box 23)
  - 1944 (Box 23)
  - 1945 (Box 23)
  - 1946 (Box 23)
  - 1947 (Box 23)
  - 1948 (Box 23)
  - 1949 (Box 23)
  - 1950 (Box 23)
  - 1951-1955 (Box 23)
  - 1956 (Box 23)
  - 1957 (Box 23)
  - 1958 (Box 23)
  - 1959 (Box 23)
  - 1960 (Box 23)
  - 1961 (Box 23)
  - undated (Box 23)
- Miscellaneous
  - Albion College, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Business affairs and the Ypsilanti Reed Furniture Company, circa 1935-1949 (Box 24)
  - Miscellanea, circa 1935-1956 (Box 24)
  - Business miscellanea, 1946-1961 (Box 24)
  - Investments miscellanea, 1958-1961 (Box 24)
  - Invitations, announcements, calling cards, etc., 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Pamphlets (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 24)
- Photographs
  - Grand Rapids Varnish Corporation (Box 24)
  - Campaigns (Box 24)
  - Portraits of Howard C. Lawrence (Box 24)
- Notebooks
  - Appointment books, address books, notebooks with political information, 1916-1960 (Box 25)
Selective Index to Correspondence
Adams, Evyn
(Methodist missionary to Japan)
1951-1966
Anderson, Charles F.
(Grand Rapids Varnish Company)
1940's-1960
Andrews, Harold F.
1940's-1960
Andrews, Roger, 1874-1943.
1934-1936
Atwood, Orville E.
(Michigan Secretary of State)
1935
Baldwin, R, W.
(Albion College trustee)
1940's-1960
Barnes, M. H.
(Barnes-Carruthers Agency, Chicago)
1934-1950
Bass, Louis
(Bass-Luckoff, Detroit)
1936, 1938-1940
Battley, Joseph F., 1893-
(National Paint, Varnicshand Lacquer Association, Inc., Washington D.C.)
1944-1961
Bicknell, John W.
(People's American State Bank, Saginaw, Michigan)
1933-1938
Blodgett, John Wood, 1860-1951.
Businessman, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1934-1951
Blood, W. J.
(Albion College trustee)
1940's-1960
Brake, D. Hale, 1891-
(Member Michigan Legislature)
1940's and 1950's
Bricker, John W. (John William), 1893-
(Governor of Ohio)
Nov. 13, 1942
Bridges, Styles, 1898-
(United States Senator from New Hampshire)
June 6, 1940, Nov. 21, 1942
Brown, Harry J.
(Grand Rapids Paint and Enamel Company)
1940's
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-
(United States Senator, Albion College trustee)
1936, 1940, 1942-1961
Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-
(Governor of Michigan)
Mar. 29, 1934, July 13, 1935, July 23, 1935, July 25, 1935, July 28, 1935, Aug. 19, 1935
Sept. 10, 1935, Apr. 18, 1936, Oct. 1 1936, Oct. 2, 1936, Feb. 21, 1938, May 17, 1939
May 18, 1939, July 25, 1940, July 27, 1940, Mar. 15, 1960
Brundage, Ray O., 1881-
(Michigan Bankers Association)
1935, 1939, 1941-1945
Bryant, Everett
(Grand Rapids Varnish Company)
1940's-1961
Butler, Leslie Anderson, 1880-
(Michigan Republican State Central Committee)
1940
Chapman, Fred A., 1878-1938.
(Ypsilanti-Reed Furniture Company; warden Ionia Reformatory; Grand Rapids Varnish Company)
Feb. 17, 1935, Feb. 19, 1935, May 2, 1936, May, 1936, May 20, 1936, Oct. 9, 1936, Oct. 31, 1936, Dec. 23, 1936
Closterhouse, Leon T.
(Central Bank, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1930's-1940's
Cochran, Friend Morris, 1897-
(Albion College)
1935-1945
Cochrane, Donald F., 1881-
(Newspaper publisher, Hartford, Michigan)
1930's and 1940's
Coors, D. Stanley, 1889-
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1950's
Crawford, Fred L., 1888-1957.
(Congressman from Michigan)
Nov. 16, 1935, Jan, 20, 1935, Feb. 3, 1936, Feb. 7, 1936, Feb. 11, 1936, May 7, 1936
May 9, 1936, Nov, 17, 1936, Nov. 23, 1936, Feb. 4, 1937, Jan. 13, 1938, Aug, 21, 1938
May 29, 1942, July 8, 1942, June 30, 1943
Cudlip, William B., 1904-
(University of Michigan regent)
1945-1961
Davies, B. L.
(Michigan Seating Company, Jackson, Michigan)
1936-1961
Dean, Walter Clark, 1898-
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Degan, James E.
(Detroit.Michigan)
1935-1936
Deyo, Harry N., 1892-
(Assistant Attorney General of Michigan)
1935-1945
Dickinson, Luren Dadley, 1859-1943.
(Governor of Michigan)
Mar. 15, 1937, Mar. 17, 1937, Mar. 18, 1939, Mar. 21, 1939, May 18, 1939, May 19, 1939, May 26, 1939, Mar. 20 1940, Apr. 4, 1940, Apr. 16, 1940, July 8, 1940, Aug. 5, 1940, Aug. 16, 1940, Sept. 11, 1940, Sept. 13, 1940, Oct. 3, 1940, Jan. 5, 1943
Dodge, Joseph M. (Joseph Morrell), 1890-
(Detroit Banker)
1941-1961
Dunckel, Miller Lewis, 1899-
(Three Rivers, Michigan; member, Michigan Legislature)
1938
Emery, John Garfield, 1881-
(American Home Security Bank, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1930's
Fead, Louis H., 1877-1943.
(Chief Justice, Michigan Supreme Court)
Jan. 13, 1937, Mar. 18, 1937, Apr. 19, 1937, Apr. 22, 1937
Ferguson, Homer, 1889-
(United States Senator from Michigan)
May 15, 1942, May 20, 1942, Nov. 12, 1942, Feb. 15, 1944, Feb. 17, 1944, Feb. 19, 1944, Feb. 21, 1944, Feb. 24, 1944
Field, Howard A.
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Fink, George Rupert, 1886-
(Great Lakes Steel Corporation)
1936-ca. 1945
Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939
(Governor of Michigan)
1933-1939
Fleenor, Wayne Harrison, 1902-
(Albion College)
1930's-1961
Flynn, Felix H. H., 1881-
(Cadillac, Michigan; member, Michigan Legislature
Sept. 28, 1934, Sept. 29, 1934, Sept. 9, 1935
Ford, Gerald R., 1913-
(Congressman from Michigan)
ca. 1950-1961
Frey, James G., 1896-
(Battle Creek, Michigan; member, Michigan Legislature
Mar. 30, 1934, Apr. 6, 1934, Apr. 5, 1935, Mar. 5, 1937, Mar. 8, 1937, Mar. 22, 1937, Mar. 24, 1937, Mar. 25, 1937, Aug. 15, 1937, Aug. 31, 1937, July 28, 1938, Nov. 7, 1938
Fritsche, Carl B.
(Dearborn, Michigan)
1935-1936
Frost, Joseph D, 1888-
(Frost and Company, Detroit)
1936-1961
Gill, Etta Margaret Lawrence, 1919-
(Daughter of Howard C. Lawrence)
1930's-1961
Glass, Harry
(American Home Security Bank, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1930's and 1940's
Goebel, Paul Gordon, 1901-
(Grand Rapids, Michigan businessman and mayor)
Late 1950's-1961
Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936.
(Governor of Michigan)
June 21, 1921, July 13, 1921, Apr, 15, 1934, Feb.-May 1935, Sept. 1935-Nov. 1936
Green, Helen A. Kelly
(Wife of Fred W. Green)
1940-1941
Groesbeck, Alexander J., 1873-1953.
(Governor of Michigan)
Mar. 26, 1934, Apr. 13, 1939, Apr, 23, 1939
Hager, Joseph A.
(Grand Rapids Varnish Corporation)
1940's-1961
Hamilton, John Daniel Miller, 1892-
(Chairman, Republican National Committee)
Feb. 10, 1937, Feb. 19, 1917, Mar. 5, 1937, July 24, 1940, Aug. 13, 1940, Sept. 5, 1940
Hayes, H. Jaye
(Hayes Manufacturing Company, Detroit)
Jan. 18, 1918, Mar. 19, 1918, Apr. 9, 1918, Apr. 26, 1918, May 15, 1918
Hekman, Edward John, 1914-
(Hekman Biscuit Company, Grand Rapids)
1940's
Hewitt, Charles Henry, 1900-
(Reconstruction Finance Corporation, Detroit)
Hill, Merrick.
Oct. 1935-1936, 1939-1941
Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.
(Congressman from Michigan)
Dec. 15, 1936, Dec. 16, 1936, Mar. 2, 1937, Mar. 9, 1937, Mar. 16, 1937, June 25, 1941
Hollinshead, Kenneth J.
(Albion College)
1930's-1961
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.
Nov. 17, 1934
Huckle, Thomas O., 1881-
(Newspaper publisher, Cadillac, Michigan)
Oct. 4, 1934, Feb. 19, 1935, Jan. 5, 1936, Jan. 7, 1936, Jan. 23, 1936, Apr. 6, 1936
Apr. 15, 1936, Dec. 10, 1936, June 21, 1939
Innis, Ralph B.
(Kansas City businessman)
1930's-1961
Jayne, Ira Waite, 1882-
(Judge)
May 25, 1942
Jonkman, Bartel J. (Bartel John), 1884-
(Congressman from Michigan)
July 3, 1940, July 26, 1940, July 29, 1940, Sept. 11, 1940, Sept. 23, 1940, Nov. 12, 1940, June 26, 1942
Kelly, Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-
(Secretary of State and Governor of Michigan)
Aug. 3, 1939, Nov. 29, 1939, Dec. 14, 1939, Apr. 13, 1942, June 8, 1942, June 19, 1942
Apr. 4, 1944, May 1, 1945
Kilpatrick, Lester A.
(Pastor, First Methodist Church, Grand Rapids)
1933-1957
Kimball, LeRoy Elwood, 1888-
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Kingston, George B
(Grand Rapids Varnish Company)
1940's-1960
Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.
(Secretary of the Navy)
Apr.-May 1935, Aug.-Nov. 1935, Jan. 11.1936, Jan. 14, 1936, July 22, 1936, Jan. 6, 1940, Jan. 8, 1940, Jan. 11, 1940, Dec. 28, 1942, Jan. 5, 1943, May 22, 1942, June 28, 1942
Kresge, Sebastian Spering, 1867-1966.
May 22, 1942, June 28, 1942
Kresge, Stanley Sebastian, 1900-
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-
(Republican Presidential, Nominee)
Aug. 7, 1936, Aug. 14, 1936, Oct. 30, 1936, Oct. 31, 1936
Lang, Samuel.
(Albion College trustee)
1950's-1961
Lawrence, Gordon D., 1930-
(Son of Howard C. Lawrence)
ca. 1940-1961
Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1916-
(Son of Howard C. Lawrence)
1933-1961
Lawrence, Luther E., 1914-
(Son of Howard C. Lawrence)
1930's-1961
Lawrence, Paul R., 1922-
(Son of Howard C. Lawrence)
1930's-1961
Lawrence, Walter A., 1932-
(Son of Howard C. Lawrence)
1945-1961
Leffler, Emil, 1899-
(Albion College)
1930's-1961
Lillie, Guy.
(Michigan Trust Company, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1930-1944
Linderholm, C. Lincoln.
(Central Bank, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1930's-1960
Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1902-
(United States delegate to the United Nations)
Oct. 31, 1957, Sept. 30, 1958
Lonergan, Augustine, 1874-1947.
(Senator from Connecticut)
Dec. 3, 1936, Dec. 9, 1936
McCartner, W. C.
(Lake Odessa Savings Bank)
1930's-1950
McCrea, Archie Elbert, 1880-
(Newspaper publisher, Muskegon, Michigan)
1930's-1961
McCurdy, Allan.
(Grand Rapids National Bank)
1930's
McKay, Frank D.
(Grand Rapids, Michigan; State Treasurer)
Nov. 2, 1935, Mar. 24, 1936, Apr. 29, 1936, Nov. 4, 1936, Nov. 16, 1936
June 3, 1937, June 7, 1937, June 17, 1937, June 19, 1937, June 23, 1937, June 28, 1937, July 1, 1937
July 12, 1938, Dec. 23, 1938, Nov. 16, 1939, Nov 20, 1939, Dec. 25, 1939, Jan.-Sept., 1940, Dec. 25, 1940, May-June 1941, July 16, 1942, Feb. 1944, Apr. 1944, May 17, 1944, Nov. 6, 1951
Mapes, Carl Edgar, 1874-1939.
(Congressman from Michigan)
May 26, 1939, May 27, 1939, May 31, 1939, Oct. 23, 1939, Oct. 25, 1939
Marin, Fredrik, 1898-
(Bank of Lansing)
1930's-1961
Mayberry, William A.
(Albion College trustee)
1950's-1961
Moody, Blair, 1902-1954.
(United States Senator)
Jan. 19, 1942, May 15, 1951
Moore, Andrew L., 1870-
(Pontiac, Michigan; member, Michigan Legislature)
Apr. 4, 1934, Apr. 9, 1934, Apr. 13, 1934, Apr. 16, 1934
Morgenthau, Henry, 1891-
(United States Secretary of the Treasury)
Jan. 4, 1942
Moulton, Vern, 1880-
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Newhall, R. Frank, 1874-
(First National Bank Chicago)
Feb. 17, 1919, Mar. 24, 1919, Mar. 27, 1919, Apr. 1919
Nicholson, Walter G.
(Detroit, Michigan)
Nov. 22, 1918, Dec. 2, 1918, Dec. 14, 1918